RG 062:024, Town of Chaplin
Connecticut State Library
Town of Chaplin records
1822-1927
Connecticut State Library
Chaplin (Conn.)
14 cubic feet
Financial and tax records for the town of Chaplin.
RG062_024
T000496
Historical Note
The town of Chaplin was incorporated in 1822 and was taken from Windham, Mansfield and Hampton.
Scope and Content
Financial and tax records for the town of Chaplin.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Chaplin -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Chaplin -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Chaplin -- Registers; Property Tax -- Connecticut -- Chaplin -- Registers
Places:
Chaplin (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1822-1927
  - Financial records including accounts, purchase orders, audits, annual reports, checks, dog licenses, treasurers' accounts, 1916-1927 (Box Box 1)
  - Tax Abstracts
    Boxes 6 and 13 are on oversize shelving.
    - 1822-1839, 1841 (Box Box 2)
    - 1836, 1837, 1838, 1839 (Box Box 3)
    - 1851, 1852, 1854, 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 4)
    - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865, 1866, 1867, 1868 (Box Box 5)
    - 1870, 1871, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 6)
    - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884 (Box Box 7)
    - 1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889 (Box Box 8)
    - 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899 (Box Box 9)
    - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905 (Box Box 10)
    - 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 11)
    - 1911, 1912, 1913 (Box Box 12)
    - 1914, 1915, 1916 (Box Box 13)
    - 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923 (Box Box 14)